"lang"
{
"Language"	"schinese"
"Tokens"
{
"Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"%subscription% 出版商 Telltale 希望与您保持联系。 请在下面输入您的电子邮件地址以订阅 Telltale 的新闻简报，它包括新游戏通知、开发过程的幕后揭秘、滑稽片断、烹饪和读者问答专栏以及临时性的特别服务。 您绝不会为自己的选择感到失望！"
"[english]Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"Telltale, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to stay in touch with you. Please enter your email address below to sign up for Telltale's newsletter, which includes new game announcements, behind-the-scenes peeks into the development process, comics, cooking and advice columns, and the occasional special offer. You'll be glad you did!"
"Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"%subscription% 的发行商 SEGA 为您提供了 Subside Sports 特别折扣，以此感谢您的购买。请在下面输入您的电子邮件地址以接收 10% 折扣礼券，它对 Subside Sports 网上商店中提供的所有产品均适用。"
"[english]Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"SEGA, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to offer you a special discount at Subside Sports as thanks for your purchase. Please enter your email address below to receive your 10% off voucher good towards any product available at Subside Sports' online store."
"Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"如果您想与Two Tribe保持联系，您可以订阅我们的时讯邮件。只需输入您的邮箱地址，我们会将有关我们游戏的最新信息定期发送到你的邮箱里。"
"[english]Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"If you want to stay in touch with Two Tribes you can subscribe to our newsletter. Simply fill in your e-mail address and we'll provide you with regular updates about all the cool games that we make!"
"charity_title"	"席德梅尔之文明 5"
"[english]charity_title"	"Sid Meier's Civilization V"
"charity_imagetext"	"回报"
"[english]charity_imagetext"	"Giving back"
"charity_header"	"2K Games 为4个基础教育慈善机构捐助了总计 $250,000，玩家的选择将会影响这批资金的送达方式。我们会统计顾客的投票并按照你们的意愿来送达这批资金。我们也很欢迎 NVIDIA 基金会，他们以捐助 $20,000 的方式主动参与了我们的计划。"
"[english]charity_header"	"2K Games is donating a total of $250,000 to four education-based charities, and users' choices will determine how the money is dispersed. We'll tally up customers' votes and disperse the funds as you have directed. We also welcome The NVIDIA Foundation, who are joining us in this initiative by donating an additional $20,000 to the program."
"charity_choice"	"你最支持哪一个慈善机构呢？"
"[english]charity_choice"	"Which charity would you like to support?"
"charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute（中亚协会）"
"[english]charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"charity_asia_details"	"在巴基斯坦和阿富汗，中亚研究所(Central Asia Institute)促进基础社区的教育，尤其是对女孩子的帮助。我们已经帮助建立了超过150所学校，已为64000名学生提供了教育机会。如果您想了解更多关于中亚研究所和分分为和平(Pennies for Peace)的信息，请致电 406-585-7841 或者浏览我们的网站 www.ikat.org。中亚研究所(Central Asia Institute) 和 分分为和平(Pennies for Peace) 的名称使用，已经通过他们的许可。其中没有任何代言，明示或暗示的任何产品，服务，公司或个人的意图。"
"[english]charity_asia_details"	"Central Asia Institute promotes and supports community-based education, especially for girls, in Pakistan and Afghanistan. We have helped establish over 150 schools and have provided education opportunities for 64,000 students. For more information about Central Asia Institute or Pennies for Peace, please call us at 406-585-7841 or visit www.ikat.org. The Central Asia Institute and Pennies for Peace names are used with its permission, which in no way constitutes an endorsement, expressed or implied, of any product, service, company or individual."
"charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa（为非洲建造学校）"
"[english]charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"charity_schools_details"	"为非洲建立希望工程学校，是一个尊重人道主义的表现。我们相信，通过教育，可以为非洲的人民带来独立的权利，让他们摆脱剥削，疾病等生活困难。在喀麦隆的乡村，家庭收入仅为 1 美元/周 的地区，我们建立用水干净、如厕卫生、粮食充盈、工具先进的希望学校。由于我们已经贡献了我们的所有积储来建设的这些学校，因此，每所学校的只需要 20,000 美元 的费用。我们所收到的每一分每一毫都将用于建立希望学校，绝对没有任何减扣。请您帮助我们，我们为此感激不尽。"
"[english]charity_schools_details"	"Building Schools for Africa is a small humanitarian organization that believes that the best way to help people to become independent of poverty, disease and exploitation is through education. We build schools with clean water and toilet and tools and seed to grow food in rural Cameroon where farming families earn about $1 per week. We can provide all this for just $20,000 per school and because we pay all our own expenses, every penny that we raise is spent on building schools with absolutely no deductions. Thanks for your help."
"charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"[english]charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"charity_read_details"	"阅读室(Room to Read®)是通过提高认字能力，减少性别歧视，来为数百万孩童提供更好的教育、发展空间。我们与当地社区，合作伙伴组织和各国政府携手共进，一起来改善小学生的阅读能力，为女孩提供需要的技能和支持，以更好地完成他们的中学教育。 如果您想知道更多的详细信息，请浏览 www.roomtoread.org。"
"[english]charity_read_details"	"Room to Read® seeks to transform the lives of millions of children in the developing world by focusing on literacy and gender equality in education. Working in collaboration with local communities, partner organizations and governments, we develop literacy skills and a habit of reading among primary school children and ensure girls have the skills and support needed to complete their secondary education. Learn more at www.roomtoread.org."
"charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"[english]charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"charity_scholarship_details"	"美国奖学金(Scholarship America®)是一个国际教育服务机制，它为即将高中毕业的，准备踏进大学的学生提供资金帮助。我们有三个核心项目促进我们更快地达到理想目标：美金奖学金(Dollars for Scholars®)，奖学金管理服务(Scholarship Management Services®)，和 梦想追寻(Dreamkeepers)。自1958年来，美国奖学金(Scholarship America) 向170多万学生，派发超过20亿美元的奖学金援助。如果您想了解更多我们的信息，尽在 www.scholarshipamerica.org。"
"[english]charity_scholarship_details"	"Scholarship America® is a national education service organization that mobilizes support for students getting into and graduating from college. We have three core programs that help us achieve our mission: Dollars for Scholars®, Scholarship Management Services®, and Dreamkeepers. Scholarship America has distributed more than $2 billion in scholarship assistance to more than 1.7 million students since 1958. More information is available at www.scholarshipamerica.org."
"charity_footer"	"投票将在美国东部标准时间2010年12月31日下午11:59结束。每人仅限一票。并非所有地区的用户可投票。欲知详情请查看 NVIDIA 基金会网站。"
"[english]charity_footer"	"Voting closes at 11:59PM EST on December 31, 2010. One vote per user. Not valid in all territories. For more information on The NVIDIA Foundation visit "
"charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"[english]charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"charity_launchgame"	"启动游戏"
"[english]charity_launchgame"	"Launch game"
}
}
