"lang"
{
"Language"	"japanese"
"Tokens"
{
"Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"%subscription% のパブリッシャー、Telltale 社がお客様への情報の配信を希望しています。 Telltale 社のニュースレターを購読する場合は、以下に電子メールアドレスを入力してサインアップしてください。ニュースレターでは、新作ゲームのお知らせ、ゲーム開発の舞台裏情報、コミック、クッキングや相談のコラム、そして特典情報（不定期）を配信しています。充実のコンテンツにきっと満足いただけるでしょう！"
"[english]Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"Telltale, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to stay in touch with you. Please enter your email address below to sign up for Telltale's newsletter, which includes new game announcements, behind-the-scenes peeks into the development process, comics, cooking and advice columns, and the occasional special offer. You'll be glad you did!"
"Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"お客様のご購入に感謝の意を込めて、%subscription% のパブリッシャー SEGA より Subside Sports の割引チケットを進呈いたします。Subside Sports のオンラインストアで利用できる 10% オフクーポンをゲットするには、メールアドレスを入力してください。"
"[english]Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"SEGA, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to offer you a special discount at Subside Sports as thanks for your purchase. Please enter your email address below to receive your 10% off voucher good towards any product available at Subside Sports' online store."
"Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"Two Tribes の最新情報をお求めの場合は、ニュースレターにご登録ください。 メールアドレスを入力していただければ、Two Tribes のクールなゲームについての最新情報を定期的にお届けします。"
"[english]Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"If you want to stay in touch with Two Tribes you can subscribe to our newsletter. Simply fill in your e-mail address and we'll provide you with regular updates about all the cool games that we make!"
"charity_title"	"Sid Meier's Civilization V"
"[english]charity_title"	"Sid Meier's Civilization V"
"charity_imagetext"	"お返しする"
"[english]charity_imagetext"	"Giving back"
"charity_header"	"2K Gamesは合計$250,000を4つの教育義捐活動に寄付します。どのように支援金が配分されるかはユーザーの意思に基づきます。ユーザーの投票を集計し、結果に基づいて基金の配分されます。 弊社に賛同し$20,000をプログラムに提供してくれたNVIDIA Foundationを歓迎します。"
"[english]charity_header"	"2K Games is donating a total of $250,000 to four education-based charities, and users' choices will determine how the money is dispersed. We'll tally up customers' votes and disperse the funds as you have directed. We also welcome The NVIDIA Foundation, who are joining us in this initiative by donating an additional $20,000 to the program."
"charity_choice"	"どの慈善事業を支援したいですか?"
"[english]charity_choice"	"Which charity would you like to support?"
"charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"[english]charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"charity_asia_details"	"Central Asia Instituteはコミュニティベースの教育をサポートしています。特にパキスタンとアフガニスタンの女児を対象としています。今までで150以上の学校の設立を助け、64.000人の生徒に教育を受ける機会を提供してきました。 Central Asia Institute または Pennies for Peaceについての詳しい情報は406-585-7841にお電話いただくか、ウェブサイトををご覧下さい。 www.ikat.org.Central Asia Institute および Pennies for Peace の団体名は許可に基づき使用されており、いかなる製品、サービス、会社名や個人を表現したり暗示するための保証を含意しません。"
"[english]charity_asia_details"	"Central Asia Institute promotes and supports community-based education, especially for girls, in Pakistan and Afghanistan. We have helped establish over 150 schools and have provided education opportunities for 64,000 students. For more information about Central Asia Institute or Pennies for Peace, please call us at 406-585-7841 or visit www.ikat.org. The Central Asia Institute and Pennies for Peace names are used with its permission, which in no way constitutes an endorsement, expressed or implied, of any product, service, company or individual."
"charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"[english]charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"charity_schools_details"	"Building Schools for Africa は、教育こそが貧困、病気、搾取から人々を自立させる最良の方法であると考えてる小さな人道支援団体です。私たちは、1世帯当たり1週間の収入が1ドルのカメルーンの農村部に、農作業道具と作物の種、きれいな水とトイレ設備のある学校を建設しています。1校あたりの建設費は$20,000です。私共にかかる費用は全て自費出費のため、集められた募金は1セントも無駄になることなく学校建設に当てられます。ご協力いただき有難うございます。"
"[english]charity_schools_details"	"Building Schools for Africa is a small humanitarian organization that believes that the best way to help people to become independent of poverty, disease and exploitation is through education. We build schools with clean water and toilet and tools and seed to grow food in rural Cameroon where farming families earn about $1 per week. We can provide all this for just $20,000 per school and because we pay all our own expenses, every penny that we raise is spent on building schools with absolutely no deductions. Thanks for your help."
"charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"[english]charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"charity_read_details"	"Room to Read® は、教育における識字能力と男女の平等に焦点をあて、発展途上国の数百万人の子供達の人生を改善することを目的としています。地域のコミュニティやパーットナー企業、及び政府と協力して我々は、小学生の識字能力と読書の習慣の改善および、女児の中等教育の完了に必要な技術と支援を確保しています。詳しくはwww.roomtoread.org　にてご覧下さい。"
"[english]charity_read_details"	"Room to Read® seeks to transform the lives of millions of children in the developing world by focusing on literacy and gender equality in education. Working in collaboration with local communities, partner organizations and governments, we develop literacy skills and a habit of reading among primary school children and ensure girls have the skills and support needed to complete their secondary education. Learn more at www.roomtoread.org."
"charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"[english]charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"charity_scholarship_details"	"Scholarship America® は大学への入学や卒業を目指す学生の支援を目的とする教育サービス機関です。この目標を達成するための3つのコアプログラムが: Dollars for Scholars®、 Scholarship Management Services®、そして Dreamkeepersです。 Scholarship Americaは1958年より今までに20億ドル以上を170万人以上の学生に提供してきました。 詳しくはwww.scholarshipamerica.org　でご確認いただけます。"
"[english]charity_scholarship_details"	"Scholarship America® is a national education service organization that mobilizes support for students getting into and graduating from college. We have three core programs that help us achieve our mission: Dollars for Scholars®, Scholarship Management Services®, and Dreamkeepers. Scholarship America has distributed more than $2 billion in scholarship assistance to more than 1.7 million students since 1958. More information is available at www.scholarshipamerica.org."
"charity_footer"	"2010年12月31日午後11:59（米国東部標準時）に投票は終了します。1ユーザーにつき1票の登場が出来ます。有効でない地域があります。詳しくは ENVIDIA Foundation でご確認下さい。"
"[english]charity_footer"	"Voting closes at 11:59PM EST on December 31, 2010. One vote per user. Not valid in all territories. For more information on The NVIDIA Foundation visit "
"charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"[english]charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"charity_launchgame"	"ゲームを開始"
"[english]charity_launchgame"	"Launch game"
}
}
