"lang"
{
"Language"	"tchinese"
"Tokens"
{
"Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"%subscription% 的發行商 Telltale 希望能與您保持聯繫。 如果您想訂閱 Telltale 電子報，請在下面輸入您的電子郵件地址。電子報內容包括遊戲上市快報、開發過程幕後花絮、漫畫、烹飪和建議專欄，以及不定時提供的優惠。 保證讓您大呼過癮！"
"[english]Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"Telltale, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to stay in touch with you. Please enter your email address below to sign up for Telltale's newsletter, which includes new game announcements, behind-the-scenes peeks into the development process, comics, cooking and advice columns, and the occasional special offer. You'll be glad you did!"
"Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"SEGA 是 %subscription% 發行商，提供您特別的 Subside Sports 折扣，做為對您購買遊戲的感謝。請在下面輸入您的電子郵件地址以接收 10% 的折扣證明，適用於在 Subside Sports 的線上商店提供的任何商品。"
"[english]Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"SEGA, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to offer you a special discount at Subside Sports as thanks for your purchase. Please enter your email address below to receive your 10% off voucher good towards any product available at Subside Sports' online store."
"Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"若您想與 Two Tribes 保持聯繫，您可以訂閱我們的電子報。只要填入電子郵件地址，您就能定期收到本公司出品之各款酷炫遊戲的最新消息！"
"[english]Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"If you want to stay in touch with Two Tribes you can subscribe to our newsletter. Simply fill in your e-mail address and we'll provide you with regular updates about all the cool games that we make!"
"charity_title"	"《文明帝國 5》"
"[english]charity_title"	"Sid Meier's Civilization V"
"charity_imagetext"	"回饋"
"[english]charity_imagetext"	"Giving back"
"charity_header"	"2K Games 為 4 個教育性質的慈善機構進行了捐款，總共 $250,000，捐獻者將能夠選擇如何分配及發放這筆慈善金。我們將會統計捐獻者的投票票數並按照你們的意願來分配這筆基金。我們也很歡迎 NVIDIA 基金會，他們藉由捐助 $20,000 來大力支持我們的計畫。"
"[english]charity_header"	"2K Games is donating a total of $250,000 to four education-based charities, and users' choices will determine how the money is dispersed. We'll tally up customers' votes and disperse the funds as you have directed. We also welcome The NVIDIA Foundation, who are joining us in this initiative by donating an additional $20,000 to the program."
"charity_choice"	"您想要支持哪一個基金會？"
"[english]charity_choice"	"Which charity would you like to support?"
"charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"[english]charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"charity_asia_details"	"在巴基斯坦和阿富汗，中亞研究機構（Central Asia Institute）以提升及贊助社區型教育為目標，尤其是對女性的幫助。我們已經幫助建立了超過150所學校，已為64000名學生提供了教育機會。如果您想了解更多有關中亞研究機構和一元為和平（Pennies for Peace）的訊息，請致電 406-585-7841 或者瀏覽我們的網站 www.ikat.org。中亞研究機構（Central Asia Institute）和一元為和平（Pennies for Peace）是經過授權的稱呼。其中並未有任何代言、明示或暗示的任何的產品、服務、公司或個人的意圖。"
"[english]charity_asia_details"	"Central Asia Institute promotes and supports community-based education, especially for girls, in Pakistan and Afghanistan. We have helped establish over 150 schools and have provided education opportunities for 64,000 students. For more information about Central Asia Institute or Pennies for Peace, please call us at 406-585-7841 or visit www.ikat.org. The Central Asia Institute and Pennies for Peace names are used with its permission, which in no way constitutes an endorsement, expressed or implied, of any product, service, company or individual."
"charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"[english]charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"charity_schools_details"	"為非洲建立新的學校是一件尊重人道主義的表現。我們相信通過教育，可以幫助非洲人民擺脫貧困、疾病及剝削等困境。在喀麥隆的農村，家庭收入僅為 1 美元/周的地區，我们建立了有著淨水供給、乾淨廁所、良好工具與耕種種子的學校。我們平均每間學校只要花 20,000 美元就可以達到上述要求，由於我們將所有的基金投注在幫助非洲上，我們所收到的每一份捐款將不會有任何的浪費，而完全用在建立學校上。"
"[english]charity_schools_details"	"Building Schools for Africa is a small humanitarian organization that believes that the best way to help people to become independent of poverty, disease and exploitation is through education. We build schools with clean water and toilet and tools and seed to grow food in rural Cameroon where farming families earn about $1 per week. We can provide all this for just $20,000 per school and because we pay all our own expenses, every penny that we raise is spent on building schools with absolutely no deductions. Thanks for your help."
"charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"[english]charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"charity_read_details"	"樂讀室（Room to Read®）是藉由提高識字能力，減少性别歧視，來為數百萬的孩童提供更好的教育及發展空間。我們與當地的社區、合作組織及政府攜手合作，一起來改善小學生的閱讀能力，並為女性提供需要的技能和支持，以便她們能夠完成中學教育。如果您想知道更多的詳細的資訊，請瀏覽 www.roomtoread.org。"
"[english]charity_read_details"	"Room to Read® seeks to transform the lives of millions of children in the developing world by focusing on literacy and gender equality in education. Working in collaboration with local communities, partner organizations and governments, we develop literacy skills and a habit of reading among primary school children and ensure girls have the skills and support needed to complete their secondary education. Learn more at www.roomtoread.org."
"charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"[english]charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"charity_scholarship_details"	"美國獎學金（Scholarship America®）是一個國際教育服務機構，它為即將從高中畢業、準備進入大學的學生提供獎學金。我們有三個主要項目幫助我們能夠更快地達到理想目標：美金獎學金（Dollars for Scholars®），獎學金管理服務（Scholarship Management Services®），及追夢者（Dreamkeepers）。自1958年來，美國獎學金（Scholarship America®）向高達170多萬的學生，發放超過20億美金的獎學金。如果您想知道更多的資訊，請瀏覽 www.scholarshipamerica.org。"
"[english]charity_scholarship_details"	"Scholarship America® is a national education service organization that mobilizes support for students getting into and graduating from college. We have three core programs that help us achieve our mission: Dollars for Scholars®, Scholarship Management Services®, and Dreamkeepers. Scholarship America has distributed more than $2 billion in scholarship assistance to more than 1.7 million students since 1958. More information is available at www.scholarshipamerica.org."
"charity_footer"	"投票將在美東時間 2010 年 12 月 31 日下午 11:59（11:59PM EST）結束。每個人僅限投一票。僅限活動參與國家。如果您想知道更多的資訊，請瀏覽 NVIDIA 基金會網站。"
"[english]charity_footer"	"Voting closes at 11:59PM EST on December 31, 2010. One vote per user. Not valid in all territories. For more information on The NVIDIA Foundation visit "
"charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"[english]charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"charity_launchgame"	"啟動遊戲"
"[english]charity_launchgame"	"Launch game"
}
}
