"lang"
{
"Language"	"korean"
"Tokens"
{
"Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"%subscription%의 배급사인 Telltale이 정기적으로 뉴스레터를 보내 드리고자 합니다. 새 게임 소식, 개발 과정 뒷 이야기 엿보기, 만화, 조언 칼럼 및 특별 이벤트 등이 포함된 Telltale의 뉴스레터를 받아 보시려면 아래에 메일 주소를 입력하십시오. 후회하지 않을 것입니다!"
"[english]Steam_TellTale_EmailPrompt"	"Telltale, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to stay in touch with you. Please enter your email address below to sign up for Telltale's newsletter, which includes new game announcements, behind-the-scenes peeks into the development process, comics, cooking and advice columns, and the occasional special offer. You'll be glad you did!"
"Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"%subscription%의 배급사인 SEGA에서 구매에 대한 보답으로 Subside Sports에서 사용할 수 있는 특별 할인을 제공합니다. Subside Sports 온라인 상점의 모든 제품에 대해 사용 가능한 10% 할인 쿠폰을 받으려면 아래에 이메일 주소를 입력하십시오."
"[english]Steam_Football2K9_EmailPrompt"	"SEGA, the publisher of %subscription%, would like to offer you a special discount at Subside Sports as thanks for your purchase. Please enter your email address below to receive your 10% off voucher good towards any product available at Subside Sports' online store."
"Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"이메일 주소만 기입하면 Two Tribes 뉴스레터를 정기 구독하실 수 있습니다. Two Tribes에서 제작하는 모든 재미있는 게임을 뉴스레터를 통해 정기적으로 업데이트하세요!"
"[english]Steam_TwoTribes_EmailPrompt"	"If you want to stay in touch with Two Tribes you can subscribe to our newsletter. Simply fill in your e-mail address and we'll provide you with regular updates about all the cool games that we make!"
"charity_title"	"Sid Meier's Civilization V"
"[english]charity_title"	"Sid Meier's Civilization V"
"charity_imagetext"	"나누는 기쁨"
"[english]charity_imagetext"	"Giving back"
"charity_header"	"2K Games 는 4개의 교육 자선 단체에 총 250,000 달러를 기부하였으며, 이 기부금은 이용자들의 선택에 따라서 어떻게 분배될 지 결정될 것 입니다. 저희는 이용자들의 투표를 종합하여, 투표 결과대로 기부금을 분배할 것 입니다. 저희는 프로그램에 20,000 달러를 추가 기부하여, 이 행사에 참여해 주신 NVIDIA 재단에도 감사드립니다."
"[english]charity_header"	"2K Games is donating a total of $250,000 to four education-based charities, and users' choices will determine how the money is dispersed. We'll tally up customers' votes and disperse the funds as you have directed. We also welcome The NVIDIA Foundation, who are joining us in this initiative by donating an additional $20,000 to the program."
"charity_choice"	"어느 자선 단체를 후원하시겠습니까?"
"[english]charity_choice"	"Which charity would you like to support?"
"charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"[english]charity_asia"	"Central Asia Institute"
"charity_asia_details"	"Central Asia Institute는 파키스탄과 아프가니스탄에서 지역사회 기반의 교육, 특히 소녀들을 위한 교육을 촉진 및 지원하고 있습니다. 저희는 150개 이상의 학교와 관계를 수립하고, 64,000 여 명의 학생들에게 교육의 기회를 제공하고 있습니다. Central Asia Institute 또는 Pennies for Peace 프로그램에 대해서 더 자세한 정보를 원하신다면, 406-585-7841 으로 연락주시거나 인터넷 사이트 www.ikat.org 를 방문해 주십시오. Central Asia Institute와 Pennies for Peace 프로그램의 명칭은 보호받고 사용하여, 이는 어떠한 제품, 서비스, 회사, 개인의 홍보, 표현 등을 지지하지 않습니다."
"[english]charity_asia_details"	"Central Asia Institute promotes and supports community-based education, especially for girls, in Pakistan and Afghanistan. We have helped establish over 150 schools and have provided education opportunities for 64,000 students. For more information about Central Asia Institute or Pennies for Peace, please call us at 406-585-7841 or visit www.ikat.org. The Central Asia Institute and Pennies for Peace names are used with its permission, which in no way constitutes an endorsement, expressed or implied, of any product, service, company or individual."
"charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"[english]charity_schools"	"Building Schools for Africa"
"charity_schools_details"	"Building Schools for Africa 는 사람들이 빈곤, 질병, 착취에서 벗어나도록 돕는 최고의 방법은 교육이라고 믿는 소규모 인도주의 단체입니다. 저희는 농사로 1주일에 1달러를 버는 카메룬의 시골 지역에 맑은 물이 나오는 학교와 화장실을 짓고, 여러 도구와 음식이 될 씨앗을 지원합니다. 저희는 동전 하나 남김없이 이 사업에 투자하기 때문에, 이 모든 것을 학교당 20,000 달러에 제공할 수 있습니다. 여러분의 도움에 감사드립니다."
"[english]charity_schools_details"	"Building Schools for Africa is a small humanitarian organization that believes that the best way to help people to become independent of poverty, disease and exploitation is through education. We build schools with clean water and toilet and tools and seed to grow food in rural Cameroon where farming families earn about $1 per week. We can provide all this for just $20,000 per school and because we pay all our own expenses, every penny that we raise is spent on building schools with absolutely no deductions. Thanks for your help."
"charity_read"	"Room to Read"
"[english]charity_read"	"Room to Read®"
"charity_read_details"	"Room to Read® 는 교육의 남녀평등과 문맹퇴치에 집중하여, 개발도상국들의 수백만 어린이들의 삶을 바꿔놓기 위해 노력하고 있습니다. 초등학교 어린이들의 문맹퇴치, 독서 습관 형성, 여자 어린이들의 기술 습득, 중등 교육 이수를 위한 지원 사업을 하고 있으며, 모든 사업은 현지의 지역 사회, 협력 단체, 정부 기관들과 공동으로 진행하고 있습니다. 더 자세한 정보는 인터넷 사이트 www.roomtoread.org 를 방문해 주십시오."
"[english]charity_read_details"	"Room to Read® seeks to transform the lives of millions of children in the developing world by focusing on literacy and gender equality in education. Working in collaboration with local communities, partner organizations and governments, we develop literacy skills and a habit of reading among primary school children and ensure girls have the skills and support needed to complete their secondary education. Learn more at www.roomtoread.org."
"charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"[english]charity_scholarship"	"Scholarship America®"
"charity_scholarship_details"	"Scholarship America® 는 학생들이 대학에 진학하고 졸업할 수 있도록 지원하는 국립 교육 서비스 단체입니다. 저희는 저희의 사업을 위한 Dollars for Scholars®, Scholarship Management Services®, Dreamkeepers 라는 3가지의 주요 프로그램을 운영하고 있으며, 1958년 부터 170만 명 이상의 학생들에게 20억 달러 이상의 장학금을 지원하였습니다. 더 자세한 정보는 인터넷 사이트 www.scholarshipamerica.org 를 방문해 주십시오."
"[english]charity_scholarship_details"	"Scholarship America® is a national education service organization that mobilizes support for students getting into and graduating from college. We have three core programs that help us achieve our mission: Dollars for Scholars®, Scholarship Management Services®, and Dreamkeepers. Scholarship America has distributed more than $2 billion in scholarship assistance to more than 1.7 million students since 1958. More information is available at www.scholarshipamerica.org."
"charity_footer"	"투표는 동부 표준시 2010년 12월 31일 오후 11시 59분(한국시각 2011년 1월 1일 오후 12시 59분)에 종료됩니다. 투표는 한 번만 가능하며, 일부 지역에서는 불가능 할 수 있습니다. 더 자세한 정보는 NVIDIA 재단을 방문해 주십시오."
"[english]charity_footer"	"Voting closes at 11:59PM EST on December 31, 2010. One vote per user. Not valid in all territories. For more information on The NVIDIA Foundation visit "
"charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"[english]charity_footer_link"	"http://www.nvidia.com/object/corporate_community.html"
"charity_launchgame"	"게임시작"
"[english]charity_launchgame"	"Launch game"
}
}
